잘잤어?
Good morning, tiger.
푸짐한 아침식사 준비해놨어
오늘밤 힘써야 하잖아
I'm making you a big breakfast, so you
can keep up your strength for tonight.
마누라 기분 좋게 해주고
임신도 하게 해줘야해
You're gonna get me
good and pregnant.
아침에 갈곳이 없다니!
난 실직자야
I've got nowhere to go this morning.
I'm unemployed.
어떻게 살아야 할지 막막해
I don't know what
I'm gonna do with my life.
와, 갑자기 힘 빠진다!
Well, I just lost my erection.
나 어떡해야 하지?
No, I mean, what am I supposed
to do with myself?
열정을 가질 만한
뭔가를 찾아야지
You're supposed to find
your passion in life.
이제 원하는건 뭐든
할수 있잖아! 신나는 일 아냐?
You can be whatever you want
to be now. It's exciting.
하지만 당혹스러워
어디서부터 시작하지?
Yeah, but it's all so overwhelming.
I don't know where to start.
잠깐, 내가 도와줄게
Wait a second.
I can help you with this.
정리부터 해봐, 자기 적성과
능력을 목록으로 만들자구
You just need to be organized. We can
make a list of your qualifications..
그걸 직업별로 분류하는 거야
폴더하고 파일이 있어야겠네!
and categorize jobs by industry.
There could be folders and files..
자기의 징그러운 정리벽이
드디어 진가를 발휘하는구나!
Hey, this is where your hyper-organized
pain-in-the-ass stuff pays off.
맞아!
I know!
다시 힘이 솟는다!
My erection is back!
프렌즈 시즌 9
'회사로 돌아간 레이첼'
고마워요
Thank you.
나 네 커피 한모금이랑
머핀 한입 먹어도 돼?
Joey, could I have a sip of your coffee
and a bite of your muffin?
- 그래
- 고마워
- Okay.
- Thank you.
잘먹을게
Thank you.
너 배고픈 이탈리아인한테
물려본적 있니?
Phoebe, have you ever been bitten
by a hungry Italian?
미안해
요즘 돈이 좀 쪼들려서
I'm sorry.
It's just, I'm a little short on cash.
필요하면 내가 좀 빌려줄게
If you want,
I could loan you some money.
아냐, 친구들한테는
절대 돈을 빌리는게 아냐
Oh, no. I learned never to
borrow money from friends.
리처드 드라이퍼스와 서로
말 안하는 것도 돈 때문인걸
That's why Richard Dreyfuss
and I don't speak anymore.
남자 친구한테 좀 빌리지 그래?
Why don't you
just spunge off your boyfriend?
그이는 피아노 치는 실직자고
신탁 자금을 자선 단체에 줬어
Yeah, right, the unemployed piano player
who gave his trust fund to charity?
이 머핀도 그이랑
나눠 먹어야 한다고
I'm splitting the muffin with him.
그럼 이건 어때?
우리 드라마 엑스트라 할래?
Hey, how about this?
Wanna be an extra on my show?
나 넣어줄수 있어?
You could do that?
그럼, 꽤 짭짤해
원하는 만큼 할수 있고
The pay's pretty good, and you
could do it for as long as you need.
- 와! 내가 TV에 나오다니!
- 피비..
- Oh, my God. I'm gonna be on TV!
- Okay, now..
TV에 나오는거 생각처럼
화려하거나 신나지 않아
I gotta tell you, being on TV isn't
as glamorous and exciting as you think.
- 정말?
- 아니! 물론 죽이지!
- Really?
- No, it is awesome.
- 안녕
- 어서와
Hey, guys.
다들 차려입었네?
Why are you all dressed up?
엠마 데리고 레이첼 회사에
인사하러 가는 길이야
We're bringing Emma to Ralph Lauren
today to introduce her to everyone.
- 우리 엠마 귀엽지?
- 그럼
- Doesn't she look cute?
- She sure does.
그런데 머리에
왜 분홍색 리본 붙였어?
Why does she have a pink bow
taped to her head?
누구든 "아들이네요!"
소리 또 했다간
Because if one more person says,
"What a cute little boy"..
내가 두들겨 팰거거든
I'm gonna whip them
with a car antenna.
우리 엠마는 사무실에서
인기폭발일거야
I think she's gonna be
the hit of the office.
그 촌스런 블라우스와 스커트보단
더 히트 칠걸?
Yeah, she's gonna be hotter
than peasant blouses and A-line skirts.
나 파란색 리본 가져도 돼?
Can I get a blue bow?
직업 안내책 한무더기 살펴본뒤
Okay. I have looked through
a bunch of career guides..
사진복사하고 중요한데 줄쳐놨어
photocopied and highlighted
key passages..
알파벳 순으로 정리했으니까
찾아보기 쉬울거야
and put them into alphabetical folders,
so you can make an informed decision.
내가 화장실에 얼마나 있었지?
How long was I in there?
ㄱ부터 시작해볼까?
광고
Okay, let's start with the A's.
Advertising.
광고? 그거 괜찮겠는데?
Wait. Advertising, that's a great idea.
다른건 더 안볼거야?
Don't you wanna look through the rest?
굳이 안봐도 되겠는데?
광고쪽이 괜찮은것 같아
I don't think I have to hear the rest.
Advertising makes perfect sense.
시간 낭비하게 해서
미안해
Sorry you had to waste all this time.
내가 라벨 제조기랑 8시간
씨름한게 그저 시간 낭비라구?
You call eight hours alone
with my label maker wasted time?
아! 이번엔 문서절단기를
사용하면 되겠구나!
Now I'll get to use my shredder!
광고문안 나도 쓸수있어
그게 뭐 어려워?
I mean, I could write slogans.
How hard could it be, right?
"치즈: 씹을 수 있는 우유입니다"
"Cheese. It's milk that you chew."
"크래커: 치즈에겐 친구가 필요하죠"
"Crackers. Because your cheese
needs a buddy."
"포도: 그럼 입속에
수박을 넣어줄까요?"
"A grape. Because who can get
a watermelon in your mouth?"
나도 하나 생각났다
I got one.
"양말: 가족의 발 건강을 위한
최선입니다"
"Socks. Because your family's feet
deserve the best."
전문가들한테 맡기자
Honey, leave it to the pros.
광고쪽 일하는 사람 알아
I actually know someone in advertising.
어릴때 친구인데
큰 광고회사 부회장이야
I grew up with a guy who is
a vice president at a big agency.
자기 만나게 해줄게
전화 줘봐
Maybe I can get him to meet you.
Give me the phone.
"전화: 전화 가진 사람들을
가까이 이어줍니다"
"The phone. Bringing you closer
to people who have phones."
"결혼: 아무나 하는게 아닙니다"
"Marriage. It's not for everybody."
잘된것 같아, 대부분 엠마가
여자애란걸 알더라구
That went well. Almost everybody
knew that she was a girl.
엠마더러 아들이라고 한 남자한테
자기가 주먹 날린 덕이지
Yeah, after you punched that one guy
who got it wrong, word spread.
사무실 들어가서
물건좀 가지고 올게
I'm just gonna go in my office
and pick up some stuff.
- 대체 누구시죠?
- 그쪽은 누구시죠?
- Who the hell are you?
난 이 사무실 주인이에요!
I'm the hell person
whose office this is.
잘한다, 레이첼!
Good one, Rach.
개빈 미첼입니다, 당신 자리를
대신하고 있는 사람이죠
I'm Gavin Mitchell,
the person who's taking over your job.
뭐라구요?
Excuse me?
아기가 참 귀엽군요!
Your baby's so cute.
사내아이한테 왜 분홍색
리본을 달았죠?
But why would you put
a pink bow on a boy?
조이, 이것봐!
Hey, Joey. Look at me.
나 간호사야!
I'm a nurse.
그럴듯한데!
Yes, you are.
간만에 때도 벗기고
광좀 내야겠군
I think it might be time
for my sponge bath.
미안, 엑스트라랑 하도 많이
사귀다 보니 버릇이 돼서
Sorry, I'm just so used
to hitting on the extras.
- 어때, 흥분되지?
- 떨리고 긴장돼
- So are you excited about your scene?
- Yeah, but I'm a little nervous.
긴장 풀어, 괜찮아, 넌 잘할거야
보나마나 그냥 뒤에 서있으라고 할거야
Relax. Don't be. They'll probably
just make you stand in the background.
좋습니다!
거기! 이리와요
- Good.
- You. Here, come here. Here.
이 쟁반 들고 여기 노란 표시
있는곳에 서있어요
Take this tray, stand on this yellow mark.
You're gonna move on "action."
큐 들어가면 움직이는 겁니다
저기 수술대 앞 파란표시까지
걸어간 다음 쟁반을 내려놔요
Walk over to the operating table, stop on
the blue mark and put the tray down.
너무 빨리 걷지 말아요
Don't walk too fast.
꾸물대지도 말고
But don't dawdle.
알았어요, 뭐라구요?
Okay. Now, what?
그럼.. 액션!
And, action!
컷! 컷!
Cut! Cut.
미안해요! 미안합니다
제가 좀 떨려서요!
- I'm sorry. I'm just a little nervous.
- Well, don't be.
떨지 말아요!
큰 격려가 되네요
Okay, that helps.
액션!
And, action!
컷!
Cut!
걱정마
나도 보통 세번은 NG 내
Don't worry about it, Phoebe.
It usually takes me three takes too.
실은 여덟번이야
All right, eight.
자, 액션!
And, action!
그럼.. 광고에 대해 더
질문 할것 없나요?
So do you have any other
questions about advertising?
없습니다
대신 제 실력을 보여드리죠
No. But let me show you what I can do.
"베이글과 도넛"
"Bagels and doughnuts.
"어디에도 어울리는 둥근 맛"
Round food for every mood."
모니카가 이럴지
모른다고 경고하더군요
Monica warned me you might do that.
우리 회사에서 일자리를
줄수 있을것 같습니다
I think we might have something
for you at the agency.
- 정말입니까? 잘됐군요!
- 무보수 인턴사원 자리예요
- Really? That's great.
- It's an unpaid internship.
재미있네요, 방금 꼭
"무보수"라고 하신것 같았어요
That's funny. When you said "unpaid,"
it sounded like you said "unpaid."
한 일이년 일하면서
경험을 쌓아가는 거예요
It won't be forever. It just takes a year
or two to get good portfolio together.
일이년을 넘어뛸 수도 있는것
아닌가요? 제 실력 보셨잖아요
Well, I can skip a couple of steps, right?
I mean, you did hear my round food thing.
새로운 일에 뛰어들땐
바닥부터 시작하는 거예요
You're changing careers. No matter what
you do, you'll have to start at the bottom.
연봉을 전처럼 받으려면
몇년 기다려야 할거예요
It's gonna be years before you're making
anything near as much as you were before.
그럼, 커피는 당신이 사는거죠?
So you're paying the check, right?
상관없잖아요? 모니카
직장도 든든하고
Come on, now. Monica has a good job.
It's not like you have a family to support.
아직 부양할 자식이
있는것도 아니구요
아기 가지려고 노력중인데
모니카는 미룰 생각이 없나봐요
Actually, we're trying. I don't think
Monica is gonna want to postpone it.
오늘밤에도 임신하려고
노력해야 하죠
We're supposed to have sex tonight.
아마 지금쯤 모니카는
집에서 옷벗고 있을걸요
Actually, she's probably at home,
naked right now.
전 누가 말리지 않으면
계속 주절대는 습성이 있어요
I tend to keep talking
till somebody stops me.
침대에 누운 아내의
모습이 떠오르네요!
- I can just picture her on the bed.
- Stop!
- 그만!
- 알겠습니다
잠깐만요, 내 일을
대신하다니 무슨 뜻이죠?
Wait. What do you mean
you're taking over my job?
레이첼이 출산휴가 간 동안
제가 일을 대신하고 있습니다
While you were on your baby vacation,
I was doing your job.
휴가라구요? 젖꼭지가
A vacation? My idea
of a vacation does not involve..
쓰리도록 아픈것도
휴가라고 할수 있나요?
something sucking on my nipples
until they are raw.
샌달스 파라다이스 섬에
가본적이 없나보군요
Clearly, you've never been
to Sandals Paradise lsland.
이 사무실에 정붙이지 말아요
내가 2주 후에 돌아올 거니까
All right. Don't get too comfortable
there, because I'm back in two weeks.
모든거 원래대로 해놔요
I want everything back
the way it was.
난 댁의 취향이 마음에 안들어요
I can't say I care too much for the way
you've rearranged my office.
난 댁이 끌고 들어온 냄새가
별로 마음에 안드는데요?
I can't say I care too much
for that smell you've brought in.
- 뭐라구요?
- 레이첼? 엠마가 응가했나봐
- Excuse me?
- Rach, we have a code brown situation.
자기가 대신 좀 봐줄래?
Honey, could you please
take care of it for me?
자기도 언젠가는
한번 해봐야해!
All right, but you're gonna
have to do one sometime.
까놓고 얘기하죠
Let me just get this straight.
나 아기 낳으러 간사이
내 자리에 댁을 앉혔군요
So I go have a baby, and they send
some guy in to do my job?
댁이 없는 사이 회사 문을
닫자는 얘기도 있었죠
Well, there was talk of shutting down
Ralph Lauren altogether.
임시 직원치고는 참 건방지군요
Okay. Right.
You're very cheeky for a temp.
난 임시직원이 아닙니다
다른 부서에서 옮겨 온거죠
I'm not a temp. I was transferred here
from another department.
어떤 부서였죠?
왕재수 부?
And what department was that?
The jerk department?
오, 사람들이 재치있는
분이란 말은 안하던데
They didn't tell me
about your quick wit.
난 지우개고 그쪽은
풀이라는 얘긴 안하던가요?
Well, did they mention that
I'm rubber and you're glue?
개빈, 회장님이 기획서
마음에 들어하시더군요
- Gavin, Ralph loved your ideas.
- Hi, Mr. Zelner.
어머, 젤너 부장님
아, 레이첼
개빈과 벌써 만났군요
Rachel. I see you've met Gavin.
레이첼이 나가고 우리 모두
몹시 난감했어요
When you left us, we weren't sure
what we were gonna do.
그런데.. 개빈이 우릴
구원해줬죠, 슈퍼 개빈!
But then, Gavin to the rescue.
Super Gavin.
와, 대단하네요!
Well, that's great.
좋아요! 그럼 "슈퍼 개빈"
내가 돌아왔으니
So now, Super Gavin,
when I come back..
이제 어디로 날아갈 계획이죠?
where do you plan on flying off to?
여기 부장님께 달렸죠, 올바른 판단을
해주실 거라고 믿습니다
That's up to Mr. Zelner.
I'm sure he'll make the right decision.
와! 아부 솜씨도 "슈퍼"급이네
Super ass-kissing power.
그나저나 언제 출근하죠?
Incidentally, when are you coming back?
오늘부터요
Today.
- 2주후 라면서요?
- 난 오늘이라고 했어요
- You said two weeks.
- No, I said today.
슈퍼맨이 귀는 좀
어두운 모양이죠?
See, for a superhero,
not so much with the listening.
실례합니다
레이첼, 이제 가야 할것 같아
I'm sorry.
Rachel, we should probably go.
기저귀가 떨어져서
자기 스웨터를 대신 썼어
I ran out of diapers,
and I had to use your sweater.
- 나 스웨터 안갖고 왔는데
- 그럼, 빨리 도망가자
- I didn't bring a sweater.
- Then, we should really go.
뭐래?
So, what'd he say?
무지 화났어, 그 사람이
He can be a little rough
around the edges..
쓴 단어는 너무 과격하니까
"강아지"라고 바꿔서 말해줄게
so I'm gonna replace a word
he used a lot with the word "puppy."
"네 강아지 같은 친구가
강아지 같은 연기 제대로 못하면"
So he said, "If your puppy friend
doesn't get her puppy act together..
"네 강아지 같은 친구 모가지
당장 잘라 버릴거야!" 그랬어
I am gonna fire
her mother-puppy ass."
미안해, 나 못하겠어
난 배우가 아냐
I'm sorry. I can't do this.
I'm just not an actor.
그래! 넌 배우가 아냐!
넌 간호사야
That's right. You're not.
You're a nurse.
- 쟁반을 든 간호사!
- 조이..
- You're Nurse With Tray.
- No, Joey..
아니, 이 간호사는 조이를 몰라
친구 사귈 시간이 없거든
Nurse With Tray doesn't know Joey.
She has no time for friends.
이 여자는
수술실에서 쟁반을 날라
She gets in that operating room
and she carries that tray to the doctor..
안그러면 사람들이 죽어
because if she doesn't, people die.
누가 죽는데?
Who dies?
저기 안대 한사람!
Man With Eye Patch!
가서 네 할일을 해
Now, you get in there,
and you do your job.
- 네, 선생님
- 좋아
Yes, doctor.
한번 더 해봅시다
Okay, let's try this one more time.
기다려요, 외눈아저씨!
곧 쟁반 가져갈게요
Hang in there, Man With Eye Patch.
Your tray is coming.
액션!
And, action.
성공이다! 해냈어!
Yes, I did it! I nailed it!
와! 다음은 뭐죠?
What's next?
지금 장면 다 안끝났어요!
The rest of the scene.
좋아요!
처음부터 다시 합시다!
Okay, from the top, people.
있잖아, 이제부턴 "응가"라고
하면 안될것 같아
Hey, you know what I was thinking? I don't
know if "code brown" is the best code word.
사람들이 우리가 무슨 말하는지
아는것 같거든
I think people might know
what we're talking about.
계획이 갑자기 바뀌었어
나 출산휴가 끝났어
That's fine. Listen, sudden change of plans.
My maternity leave just ended.
오늘 출근 안하면 해고하겠대
They said if I didn't
come back today, they'd fire me.
뭐? 그건 불법이야!
What? No, that's illegal.
이 회사 노동부서가 어디야?
내가 당장 가서 얘기하면..
I'll have the Labor Department
here so fast, they won't..
진정해, 노동운동가 선생
All right, calm down, Norma Rae.
They didn't actually say that.
진짜 그렇게 말한건 아냐
당장 일 시작하지 않으면
저 인간이 내 자리 뺏을것 같아
I'm just afraid if I don't come back now,
this guy will try and squeeze me out.
엠마는 어떡하구?
아직 유모도 못 구했잖아
But what about Emma?
I mean, we don't have a nanny.
알아, 오늘 저녁에
대책을 세워 보자구
I know. We're just gonna have
to figure out a plan tonight.
오늘 엠마좀 봐줄수 있어?
Can you please just take care
of her for today?
물론이지, 찌찌만 떼어줘
그럼 바로 갈게
Absolutely. Just give me your breasts,
and we'll be on our way.
달리 방법이 없어서 그래
Come on.
I don't know what else to do.
알았어
Fine. Fine.
아빠랑 재미있게 놀거지?
그럼, 그렇구 말구
We'll have fun, won't we?
Yes, we will. Yes, we..
- 로스?
- 응?
Ross.
자기 아주 예쁘다
You're pretty.
무슨일을 하든 처음부터
새로 시작해야 할것 같아
Whatever I decide to do, I'm gonna be
starting a new career from scratch.
새로운 직업으로 자리잡기까지
시간도 좀 걸릴거구
It's gonna be a while
before I make a living at it.
아기를 갖기에 적당한 시기가
아닌것 같아
Maybe now's not the right time
to be starting a family.
당장은 아이 갖고 싶지 않다고
모니카한테 말해야겠네?
So you have to tell Monica you don't
want to have a baby right now?
맞아
Yeah.
잘있어!
Goodbye.
아기 만들 시간이야!
바지 벗어, 챈들러!
Okay, it's baby time.
Pants off, Bing.
오빠 있는줄 몰랐어!
Didn't see you there, Geller.
그래, 로스도 여기 있어
Ross is here, so..
그래, 맞아
나도 여기서 놀고 싶은데, 괜찮지?
And I was really hoping
that maybe I could hang out.
너희는 뭐하고 놀건데?
You know, what do you feel like doing?
우린 아기 만들거야
Well, we're gonna have sex.
난 그건 별로 재미없는데
I don't feel like having sex.
그러지 말고 우리 영화나 볼까?
Maybe.. I don't know. Maybe we
can watch a movie or something.
내말 잘들어
Let me put it this way:
오빠가 여기 있거나 없거나
우린 아기 만들거야
We're having sex
whether you're here or not.
바지 벗어라, 챈들러!
Pants off, Bing.
나 복귀했으니까 그동안에
있었던 일 보고해주세요
Now that I'm back, why don't you just
fill me in on what you've been up to.
컴퓨터의 '인싱크' 화면보호기를
바꿔놨습니다
Well, I've changed your screen saver
from that picture of *NSYNC.
내가 떠날때만 해도
인기 많았어요!
Hey, they were popular when I left.
내일 있을 중요한 프리젠테이션
준비가 제일 큰일이었어요
I'm working on this
big presentation for tomorrow.
내가 할거니까
진행상황을 말해주세요
I should be involved in that,
so get me up to speed.
몇주는 걸릴 겁니다, 이번
프리젠테이션은 나한테 맡기지 그래요
That'll take weeks.
Let me take care of the presentation.
아뇨, 무슨 속셈인지 알아요
No. I see what you're
doing here, all right?
하지만 이건 내 일이에요! 5년동안
해왔고, 어떻게 하는지도 잘 안다구요!
This is my job, buddy. I've had it for
five years, and I know how it works.
- 그러니까 빨리 보고나 해요
- 좋습니다
- So why don't you just catch me up.
- Fine.
의자를 엉망으로 만들었군요
Oh, God. You've totally messed
with the back support on my chair.
- 이거 어떻게 고치죠?
- 여기 5년이나 있었다면서요
- How do you fix this?
- You've been here five years.
- 알아서 해결하시지
- 좋아요! 그러죠
- You figure it out.
- Fine, I will.
됐어요, 시작할까요?
All right, fill me in.
여기 어울리는 푸른색 넥타이 있니?
엠마가 침을 흘렸어
Do you have a blue tie that would go
with this? Emma spit up on mine.
나 취직될지 모르니까
꼭 돌려줘야 한다
Yeah, but you have to give it back
if I get a job.
그때쯤이면 넥타이는
구시대 유물이 되고
Of course, by that time,
ties will be obsolete..
다들 우주복을 입겠지만
and we'll all be wearing
silver jumpsuits.
- 잘잤어, 내 사랑?
- 잘잤어?
Hey, good morning, lover.
어젯밤 이후로 무릎이
계속 후들거려
I gotta say, after last night,
I'm a little weak in the knees.
모니카, 제발! 어디 들어가거든
주위좀 살펴봐!
Here's an idea. You walk into a room,
take a quick scan.
미안해
Sorry.
내 느낌인데 왠지
어젯밤 아기 가진것 같아
But I kind of have this feeling that
we may have made a baby last night.
자기한테 할 얘기 있어
Oh, God, I have to tell you something.
자기 임신 안했어
You're not pregnant.
무슨 소리야?
What are you talking about?
아기 가지려면 해야하는
그일 말야
Well, that thing that I have to do
to make a baby?
어제 나 연기 한거야
I faked it.
뭐? 연기였다구?
What? You faked it?
저기 말야
You know what?
넥타이 필요없어
I don't need a tie.
이게 더 나을것 같아
I mean, it's better open collar,
you know?
더 편해 보이잖아
It's more casual.
조이? 나 못하겠어!
이건 말이 안돼!
Joey. Listen, I can't do this.
It doesn't make any sense.
어제는 간호사였는데
오늘은 웨이트리스라구?
Yesterday I was a nurse,
and today I'm a waitress at a cafe?
엑스트라는 원래 여러 역할을
하는 경우가 많아, 괜찮아
Sometimes we use the same extras
for different parts. It's okay.
난 안괜찮아! 난 어제 간호사로
인상적인 연기를 펼쳤어!
Well, it's not okay, because I gave a very
memorable performance as the nurse.
그런데 갑자기 웨이트리스라니?
내 팬들이 혼란스러울거야!
And now, suddenly, I'm the waitress?
That's gonna confuse my fans.
넌 간호사지만
Well, maybe you are a nurse..
아르바이트로
웨이트리스 일도 하는거야
but you moonlight as a waitress.
홀로 두 아이를 키우고 있는
엄마이기 때문이지
Because I'm a single mother
supporting my two children.
- 좋았어!
- 그래
Nice.
잠깐
Wait a minute.
닥터 드레이크와 난 같은 병원에서
일하니까 인사해야하지 않을까?
Dr. Drake Ramoray and I work at the
same hospital. Wouldn't I come say hi?
안돼, 넌 닥터 드레이크와
심하게 싸웠어
No. No, see, you and Drake
are having a fight.
뭐 때문에?
About what?
너랑 잠을 잔뒤
He slept with you..
Best sex you ever had, by the way.
전화를 걸지 않았거든
And then never called you.
그리고 난 데비와 베키의
새 아빠를 찾고 있지
And I just wanted a new daddy
for Davey and Becky.
그래, 그럼 처음부터 갑니다!
Okay. Okay, from the top.
액션!
And, action.
내 점심초대에 응하다니
놀랍군
So I'm surprised you agreed
to have lunch with me.
내 자신도 놀라워
그래도 난 여기왔어
I'm surprised too. But yet, here I am.
컷! 컷!
Cut! Cut!
뭐하는 거예요?
What are you doing?
이사람, 나랑 같이 잠 자놓고
연락을 끊어서 화가 났어요
I'm very angry at him because he slept
with me and never called me back.
- 나도요!
- 나도!
- Me too.
- Me too!
진정해요! 설정이 그렇다는 거예요
Calm down. She means on the show.
엑스트라 물갈이 해야겠네!
We need some new extras
around here.
벌써 왔어요?
Wow. You're here already.
프리젠테이션에 대해 연구하느라고
엠마랑 좀 일찍 왔어요
Yes. Emma and I came in a little early
to do research on the presentation.
내가 몇군데 고쳤어요
어쨌든 전부 다 이해했으니까
Actually, I made a few changes.
I think I'm caught up on everything.
뭐든지 물어봐요
So ask me anything.
- 의자는 어떻게 고치죠?
- 그거만 빼구요!
- How do you fix the chair?
- Except that!
부장님, 오후에 있을 프리젠테이션
준비 다 마쳤어요
Hello, Mr. Zelner. We are all ready
for our presentation this afternoon.
- 다행이군요, 10분 후에 시작합니다
- 네? 안돼요
- Good, because it's in 10 minutes.
- What? I can't do that. I have the baby.
애 아빠가 한시간 후에나
애를 데리러 올텐데요
Ross is not gonna pick her up
for an hour.
그럼 개빈이 발표해요
지금해야 합니다
Then Gavin can give the presentation.
We have to do it now.
회장님이 일찍 나가셔야 한대요
헬리콥터 사러 가신답니다
Ralph needs to leave early today.
He's going helicopter shopping.
하지만 존경하는 분입니다
지옥까지 따라갈수 있어요
But I love that man.
I'd follow him into hell.
도청장치
Microphones.
축하해요
댁이 이겼군요
Well, there you go, you win.
You win.
발표 잘하고 칭찬 많이 받아요
You get to do the presentation.
You'll knock them dead.
내가 여기서 일했다는건 아무도 기억
못할 거예요, 회장이 헬리콥터 사면
No one will remember that I worked here,
and then Ralph will buy his helicopter..
슈퍼 개빈은
그 옆에서 신나게 날아가겠죠
and Super Gavin will just fly
right alongside of him.
- 당신이 프리젠테이션 해요
- 애가 있어서 못해요
- You can do the presentation.
- No, I can't. I have a baby.
내가 봐줄게요
I'll watch her.
왜 호의를 베풀죠?
Why would you do that?
당신 일이고 애 많이 썼잖아요
또 당신이 살짝 돈것 같아서요
Because you worked really hard, and
it's your job. And you're a little crazy.
정말 고마워요!
That's really nice.
미리 말하지만 난 우는 여자
굉장히 불편해요
I should tell you that crying women
make me very uncomfortable.
그럼 아주 불편해지겠네요
Well, you're not gonna like
what's coming.
오, 미안해요!
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
세상에
God.
정말 고마워요
Thank you. Thank you.
걱정 말아요
난 애를 잘보니까
I'm really fine. Don't worry.
I'm great with children.
개빈 미첼이라고 해요
만나서 반갑습니다
Gavin Mitchell. Pleased to meet you.
제친구 자르지 마세요
제가 다시 얘기해 볼게요
Please don't fire my friend.
Just let me talk to her.
- 좋아! 이번이 마지막이야!
- 고맙습니다!
- Okay, but this is her last chance.
- Thank you.
제가 은혜 갚을게요
How about I do something for you?
내일 제가.. 대머리 감출수 있게
모자 하나 갖다줄게요!
Tomorrow, I'll bring you a hat,
cover up the bald.
피비.. 이번엔
Listen, Phoebe. I was just talking
to the director..
나 때리지 말고
and he was thinking maybe
this time you don't hit Drake.
그냥 차만 날라
You just wait on the tables.
그럴순 없어! 난 배우야!
나한텐 내 스타일이 있어!
I can't do that. I'm an actor.
I have a process.
넌 맛사지사고 네가 가진건
맛사지 침대야!
You're a masseuse.
You have a table with a hole in it.
잠깐, 왜 그러는지 알겠다
너 위기감 느끼는구나
Wait, I see what's happening here.
You're threatened.
뭐?
What?
내가 연기를 너무 잘해서
시선이 나한테 집중되니까
I'm so good in the scene
that I'm stealing focus from you.
도전을 받아들여, 조이!
난 싸울 준비가 됐어!
Rise to the challenge, Tribbiani,
because I just raised the bar.
덤벼!
Come join me up here.
- 그렇게 나오다면야
- 그래
- Okay, great. I will.
- Okay, good.
쟤 잘라요! 순순히 안나갈 거니까
경비를 부르는게 좋을걸요
Yeah, you can fire her, but I would
call security. She won't go easy.
연기를 했다구?
그걸 어떻게 연기할 수가 있어?
You faked it?
You couldn't have faked it.
할수 있어
표정잡고 소리만 내면
Yes, you can. You just make
the faces and the noises.
남자들이 그럴수 있다구?
Guys can fake it?
믿을수 없어!
그건 여자들 고유영역이야!
Unbelievable.
The one thing that's ours.
그런데 임신하려고 노력하면서
왜 가짜로 연기를 해?
Why would you fake it
when we're trying to have a baby?
그게 바로 이유야
Well, that's actually why.
나 지금부터 새로 시작해야해
Look, I'm starting
a whole new career now.
애를 낳지 말자는게 아니라..
I'm not saying I don't want a baby.
조금 미루면 안될까?
I'm just saying maybe
we could wait a little while.
얼마나? 한달?
Like a month?
- 1년?
- 정말? 1년이나 미루자구?
- Or a year?
- Really? You wanna wait a year?
1년까지 안걸릴거야
내 실력 알잖아
It could be less than a year.
I mean, you've heard my stuff.
"바지: 팬티같지만 더 깁니다"
"Pants. Like shorts but longer."
1년 더 걸릴지도 모르겠다
It'll probably be more than a year.
- 난 정말 아기 갖고 싶은데
- 나도 마찬가지야
- I really wanna have a baby.
- Well, yeah, me too.
그냥 전에 하던 일 계속할까봐
Look, I'll just get my old job back.
아냐, 난 자기가 정말로
좋아하는 일 했으면 좋겠어
No, I want you to have
a job that you love..
통계분석이나 데이터 재구성하는
그런일 말고
not statistical analysis
and data reconfiguration.
내가 그만두니까
내가 하던일을 이해하게 됐어?
I quit, and you learn what I do?
아기 갖기에 적절한 시기는
따로 없을지 몰라
I think there's never gonna be
a right time to have a baby.
지금은 직장이 없지만 조만간
Now you're unemployed,
and in a little while..
새로 일 생기면 바빠질걸
you'll find a new job
that'll keep you really busy.
아기 가지면 안되는 이유는
항상있게 마련이야
There's always gonna be
a reason not to do this..
하지만 아기가 태어나면
그런 이유들은 다 잊혀져
but I think once the baby comes,
we'll forget about all those reasons.
하긴
I guess.
애가 생기는건
언제고 겁나는 일이야
I mean, it's always gonna be scary
when we have a baby.
정말 겁나는 일이지
It's gonna be really scary.
애가 생기면
I mean, God, when we have a baby..
얼마나 뒤죽박죽이겠어?
there's gonna be so much
that we're not able to control.
집안은 엉망이 될테구!
I mean, the apartment's
gonna be a mess.
그걸 치울 시간도 없을걸?
I won't have time to clean it.
아기가 리본 보관서랍 열어서
What if the baby gets
into the ribbon drawer..
뒤섞으면 어쩌지?
and messes up all the ribbons?
아기 물건이 너무 많아서
What if there's no room
for a ribbon drawer..
리본 보관할 서랍도 없을지 몰라!
because the baby's stuff
takes up all the space?
그럼 리본은 다 어디에 두지?!
Where will all the ribbons go?
자기 마음 바뀌기 전에
빨리 아기 만들까?
Should we go make a baby
before you change your mind?
제발 그러자!
- Yes, please!
- Okay.
이번엔 절대로 연기 안할게
And I promise I will not
fake it this time.
나야말로 연기하지 말아야할텐데
나 지금 충격 먹었거든
Well, I wish I could say the same.
I'm a little shook up.
그 수술 일부러 망친거 알아!
I know you botched
that operation on purpose.
내가 그걸 증명하게 되면
넌 감옥에 가게 될거야
I can't prove it yet, but when I do,
you'll be going to jail for murder.
네가 내 동생이라도 할수 없어!
I don't care if you are my brother.
난 네 동생이 아냐!
I'm not your brother.
우리 애들 어쩔 거예요, 드레이크?
What about my children, Drake?
안돼! 싫어! 싫다구요!
No! No! No!
사람 살려!
God!